{
    "id": "1bf34a05fe79468ca813ac3e498efb8c",
    "title": "Grammar Exercise (Intermediate Level)",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I met him in Germany three years .........................",
            "description": "We use ago with a past tense and a time expression to count back from the present. ",
            "answers": [
                "ago",
                "before",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5aecf603dc254778a907298c4c4462ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you been here ...........................?",
            "description": "Before can be used with a present perfect tense or past perfect tense to mean 'at any time before now/then'.",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "ago",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "786fff9204534ccb8e25488e71353821"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was in Spain two years ........................",
            "description": "We use ago with a past tense and a time expression to count back from the present. ",
            "answers": [
                "ago",
                "before",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "539c6a91fdf140b4a6d700395b5acfe4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The two girls are ........................ in looks, but not in personality.",
            "description": "Alike can mean like each other. ",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "alike",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b2d619bfd1a64fc7871f091e088939e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been round ........................ looking for the dog.",
            "description": "We can use all with some singular countable nouns to mean every part of. ",
            "answers": [
                "all village",
                "all the village",
                "whole village"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "265cd7c4a9814833a79d4187acdfef3a"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have eaten ……………….. loaf.",
            "description": "We cannot use all before definite articles.",
            "answers": [
                "all a",
                "all",
                "a whole"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "eb4b2e6e513a48f8a0705add04e4eded"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are very ..................... finished.",
            "description": "Almost cannot be used with very.",
            "answers": [
                "almost",
                "nearly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "829659dde5504694bee829dec97b5fea"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………. I don’t agree with him, I think he is sincere.",
            "description": "We use even if to talk about hypothetical situations.",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "Even if",
                "Even though"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d83767b1474a4c059a7200f4c78c20a5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have got …………….. energy than I used to have.",
            "description": "Less is the comparative form of little.",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "lesser",
                "least"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2d7eeed7555e4d3bb776bc34ebdb5ad3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Thank you very much. That was ………………. of you.",
            "description": "When most means very, the article the is not used with it.",
            "answers": [
                "most kind",
                "the most kind",
                "kindest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "230b01b81130436d8ec59cadd33f10fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "They experienced little difficulty …………….. the money.",
            "description": "After difficulty we use ‘in + ing form’.",
            "answers": [
                "to steal",
                "in stealing",
                "to stealing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "939b68f9ecfa4a898c7e8852587bfd2f"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are having ……………… weather.",
            "description": "Weather is uncountable. It cannot be used with articles.",
            "answers": [
                "a terrible",
                "terrible",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f6c61dccf49144a9a2eab54469f40829"
        }
    ]
}